import type { MCQ } from '../../../types'

export const mcqSet2: MCQ[] = [
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "The ________ stakeholders are those who do not directly work with a company.",
    "options": [
      "Primary",
      "Secondary",
      "Internal",
      "External"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "The ________ flow of communication is from lower levels to higher levels",
    "options": [
      "Downward",
      "Horizontal",
      "Upward",
      "Vertical"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "A good elevator pitch should last no longer than ________.",
    "options": [
      "1 minute",
      "1 hour",
      "20 seconds",
      "20 minutes"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "A comment like, \"Let's talk about the way we talk to each other in front of my parents.\" is most obviously a type of ______",
    "options": [
      "self-disclosure",
      "impersonal communication",
      "meta communication",
      "dialectical tension"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "Which of the following icon is used to add an attachment to an email?",
    "options": [
      "Stationary icon",
      "GIF icon",
      "Paper clip icon",
      "Emoji icon"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "The information that is known to you but unknown to others. Which quadrant is this?",
    "options": [
      "open",
      "unknown",
      "blind spot",
      "hidden"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "In which stage, a person will announce to the world about their relationship?",
    "options": [
      "integration",
      "terminating",
      "bonding",
      "initiation"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "Which of these represents a type of dialectical tensions in relationships?",
    "options": [
      "connection and autonomy",
      "openness and privacy",
      "predicatability and novelty",
      "all the above"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "Which is true of self-disclosure?",
    "options": [
      "It is viewed essentially the same way around the world.",
      "It rarely occurs incrementally.",
      "It is strongly influenced by culture.",
      "It usually occurs in large groups rather than dyads."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "________ planning is an essential component of successful business management.",
    "options": [
      "Business",
      "Organisational",
      "Powerful",
      "Effective"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  }
]
